A Register of the Arch Puddington Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound Recordings, 1951-1996 (Box 35-39)
  - Keri, Thomas, sound recording of interview, undated, 1956, and 1994 March 10
    3 compact sound cassettes. Sleeve of one undated cassette label reads: Keri-Hungarian 1956 Thomas. Use copy reference numbers: 2001c73_a_0005489, 2001c73_a_0005552
  - Latvnski, Marek, sound recording of interview, undated; 2 compact sound cassettes. Use copy reference numbers: 2001c73_a_0005555 and 2001c73_a_0005557
  - Leinwoll, Stanley, sound recording of interview, 1994 March 23; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005554
  - Lasata, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005556
  - Peyman, Karl, sound recording of interview, 1994 May 10; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005553
  - Marks, Leonard, sound recording of interview, 1996 June 6; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005558 (Box 38)
  - Marsh, Bill, sound recording of interview, 1996 June 5; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005559
  - Matthews, John, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005561
  - Matlock, Jack, sound recordingof interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005562
  - Matusevich, Vladimir, sound recording of interview, 1996 June 7; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005563
  - McCargan, James, sound recording of interview, 1994 April 19; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005564
  - Mullervey, Mary, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005565
  - Novak, Jan, sound recording of interview, 1996 April 19; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005566
  - Palous, Martin, sound recording of interview by telephone, 1994 May 2; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005568
  - Panoff, Kyrill, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005569
  - Parta, Gene, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005677
  - Pehachek, Pavel, and Lida Rakusanova sound recording of interview, 1996 July; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005678
  - Pell, Gene, sound recording of interview, 1996 June 5; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005680
  - Pomar, Mark, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005683
  - Poole, Russell, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005744
  - Raymond, Walt, sound recording of interview, 16 April; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005747
  - Revmgu(?) sound recording of interview, undated
  - Reyman, Karl, sound recording of interview, 1994 April 6; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005750
  - Richardson, John, sound recording of interview, 1996 June 4; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005805 (Box 39)
  - Reitman, Lev, and Fred Eidlin sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005806
  - Ronalds, Francois, Jr., sound recording of interview, October 3; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005807
    A woman interviews Ronalds about his time at Radio Liberty.
  - Ronalds, Ronnie, sound recording of interview of interview, 1996 June 6; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005808
  - Rowson sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005809
  - Rubin, Gene, sound recording of interview, 1994 April 4; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005810
    Among the topics covered are Rubin's career as a journalist, why he would leave his country even though he was a top sports writer, the impact of his Judaism, and censorship.
  - Ruszar, Joseph, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005811
  - Steibel, Gerald, sound recording of interview, 1996 March 27; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005812
    Steibel comments on the early days of Radio Free Europe in the 1950s. Among the topics are: how and why the purpose of RFE changed from liberation, anticommunism in RFE, the influence of the CIA, the Crusade for Freedom, the fallout from the Czech uprising, and the effect of the radios.
  - Szabados sound recording of interview, 1996 May 15; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005813
  - Tigrid, Pavel, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005817
  - Traycey, Roman, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005818
  - Vallens, Dagmara, sound recording of interview, 1996 March 22; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005819
  - Vasiliev, Rosen, sound recording of interview, 1996 April 12; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005822
  - Washbuir sound recording of interview, 1996 June 7; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005823
  - Wierzbiecki, Zbigniew, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005824
  - Wimbush, Enders, sound recording of interview, undated; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005825
  - Zaprudnik, Jan, sound recording of interview, 1994 March 29; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005829
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, sound recording of interview, 1996 May 16; Use copy reference number: 2001c73_a_0005830